{
  "type": "writing",
  "language_code": "zh-CN",
  "data": [
    {
      "question": "今年",
      "answer": "Jīnnián | this year"
    },
    {
      "question": "年",
      "answer": "Nián | year"
    },
    {
      "question": "岁",
      "answer": "Suì | year (of age)"
    },
    {
      "question": "怎么样",
      "answer": "Zěnme yàng | how is..."
    },
    {
      "question": "今天",
      "answer": "Jīntiān | today"
    },
    {
      "question": "课",
      "answer": "Kè | class, lesson"
    },
    {
      "question": "星期",
      "answer": "Xīngqí | week"
    },
    {
      "question": "上午",
      "answer": "Shàngwǔ | morning"
    },
    {
      "question": "上",
      "answer": "Shàng | above, last"
    },
    {
      "question": "下午",
      "answer": "Xiàwǔ | afternoon"
    },
    {
      "question": "下",
      "answer": "Xià | below, next"
    },
    {
      "question": "星期日",
      "answer": "Xīngqírì | sunday"
    },
    {
      "question": "生日",
      "answer": "Shēngrì | birthday"
    },
    {
      "question": "生",
      "answer": "Shēng | to be born"
    },
    {
      "question": "多大",
      "answer": "Duōdà | how old"
    },
    {
      "question": "多",
      "answer": "Duō | how (many/much)"
    },
    {
      "question": "大",
      "answer": "dà | big, large"
    },
    {
      "question": "出生",
      "answer": "Chūshēng | to be born"
    },
    {
      "question": "出",
      "answer": "Chū | to go, to come out"
    },
    {
      "question": "属",
      "answer": "Shǔ | to be born in the year of (one of the 12 animals)"
    },
    {
      "question": "聚会",
      "answer": "Jùhuì | get-together, party"
    },
    {
      "question": "会",
      "answer": "huì | meeting"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝贺",
      "answer": "Zhùhè | to congratulate"
    },
    {
      "question": "祝",
      "answer": "Zhù | to wish"
    },
    {
      "question": "参加",
      "answer": "Cānjiā | to participate, to attend"
    },
    {
      "question": "了",
      "answer": "Le | (a modal particle, aspect particle)"
    },
    {
      "question": "吃",
      "answer": "Chī | to eat"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛋糕",
      "answer": "Dàngāo | cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "蛋",
      "answer": "Dàn | egg"
    },
    {
      "question": "糕",
      "answer": "gāo | cake"
    },
    {
      "question": "买",
      "answer": "Mǎi | to buy"
    },
    {
      "question": "瓶",
      "answer": "Píng | bottle"
    },
    {
      "question": "红葡萄酒",
      "answer": "Hóng pútáojiǔ | red wine"
    },
    {
      "question": "红",
      "answer": "Hóng | red"
    },
    {
      "question": "葡萄",
      "answer": "pútáo | grape"
    },
    {
      "question": "酒",
      "answer": "jiǔ | wine or liquor"
    },
    {
      "question": "北京",
      "answer": "Běijīng | country"
    }
  ]
}
